{
    "subject": "resource/The_Carpet_Frogs",
    "predicate": "property/associatedActs",
    "object": "resource/Randy_Bachman",
    "human_readable": "The Carpet Frogs are associated with Randy Bachman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9746740460395813,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Randy Bachman and The Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9699484705924988,
            "question": "How did the association between Randy Bachman and The Carpet Frogs come about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8887349367141724,
            "question": "Are there any recordings or performances featuring both Randy Bachman and The Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8384649753570557,
            "question": "Who is associated with the Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.629196047782898,
            "question": "What type of music are The Carpet Frogs associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3413124084472656,
            "question": "What other musical projects has Randy Bachman been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28640082478523254,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the history of The Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24218867719173431,
            "question": "Can you name any famous songs by The Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19880609214305878,
            "question": "What musical group is Randy Bachman known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12370136380195618,
            "question": "What is Randy Bachman's legacy in the music industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Carpet Frogs are associated with Randy Bachman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5707_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical group is Randy Bachman known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5707_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any famous songs by The Carpet Frogs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5707_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the history of The Carpet Frogs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5707_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5707_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that The Carpet Frogs have been associated with Randy Bachman, including performing with him on the Live 8 Toronto event and being part of his tour as the backing band for The Bachman-Cummings Band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}